[
  {
"question": "A son motorboats his mom while the sister rides her. Then there is a little family bondage. Finally the whole thing culminates in the dad assisting with some big black penetration.",
"answer": "Star Wars: Episode VI - Return of the Jedi",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "BaconConnoisseur",
"upvotes": "3782",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/ezzcsu/a_son_motorboats_his_mom_while_the_sister_rides/"
},
{
"question": "Man is forced to participate in the rescue of a hostage by the government, that has turned his residence into a refugee camp",
"answer": "District 9",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "Skybots10",
"upvotes": "2653",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/efkrwa/man_is_forced_to_participate_in_the_rescue_of_a/"
},
{
"question": "Boy goes on a trip to meet his family and leaves once he ensures two of his relatives are going to have sex",
"answer": "Back to the Future",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "thefilthyape",
"upvotes": "2133",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/dncgrp/boy_goes_on_a_trip_to_meet_his_family_and_leaves/"
},
{
"question": "In pursuit of ultimate power, a purple being must have a young woman sacrifice. At the end of the film, the purple being achieves ultimate power, but is severely wounded in the chest by a vengeful prince.",
"answer": "Avengers: Infinity War",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "jsilvy",
"upvotes": "1982",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/dptapg/in_pursuit_of_ultimate_power_a_purple_being_must/"
},
{
"question": "Let's just ban Infinity War/Endgame posts for good, yes?",
"answer": "N/A",
"category": "Meta",
"author": "[deleted]",
"upvotes": "1954",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/e972w2/lets_just_ban_infinity_warendgame_posts_for_good/"
},
{
"question": "Little guy works overtime while also stealing body parts from his dead coworkers before ditching his job to go on a cruise with his unconscious girlfriend",
"answer": "WALL-E",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "davidfromthelobster",
"upvotes": "1940",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/e1vvcf/little_guy_works_overtime_while_also_stealing/"
},
{
"question": "An overweight loner with poor hygiene and social skills goes on a quest to get rid of the minorities invading his homeland.",
"answer": "The Lord of the Rings",
"category": "Fantasy",
"author": "Jdoggcrash",
"upvotes": "1702",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/dipxt5/an_overweight_loner_with_poor_hygiene_and_social/"
},
{
"question": "Fe-male",
"answer": "Iron Man",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "jsilvy",
"upvotes": "1677",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/eyfvjs/female/"
},
{
"question": "(TV Series) 112 year old man grooms 14 year old girl under the watchful eyes of her 16 year old brother.",
"answer": "Twilight",
"category": "Fantasy",
"author": "Alpha741",
"upvotes": "1589",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/gvs80u/tv_series_112_year_old_man_grooms_14_year_old/"
},
{
"question": "Guys wife dies so he gets high.",
"answer": "Up",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "Almym",
"upvotes": "1536",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/eac9iq/guys_wife_dies_so_he_gets_high/"
},
{
"question": "After a famous guy dies from constructive criticism, one of his fans abandons his homeless family and continues on the dead man’s legacy by manipulating a twink",
"answer": "Joker",
"category": "Drama",
"author": "night-moth",
"upvotes": "1531",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/1hcuqcc/after_a_famous_guy_dies_from_constructive/"
},
{
"question": "The big bad guy kills the main bad guy because he failed to kill their bad guy who was almost killed trying to kill a bad guy.",
"answer": "Avengers: Endgame",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "[deleted]",
"upvotes": "1493",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/fmhxjk/the_big_bad_guy_kills_the_main_bad_guy_because_he/"
},
{
"question": "An old man and his fresh, young partner are tailing a madman, who has been punishing people who exemplify the deadly sins in morbidly fitting ways. It all comes to a head in the dessert, where he reveals wrath and envy are the final sins. ",
"answer": "Se7en",
"category": "Thriller",
"author": "Buttpounder90",
"upvotes": "1478",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/1hygzug/an_old_man_and_his_fresh_young_partner_are/"
},
{
"question": "Skinny kid makes a black friend, father doesn’t approve.",
"answer": "Iron Man",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "Excaliber596",
"upvotes": "1455",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/jn8y36/skinny_kid_makes_a_black_friend_father_doesnt/"
},
{
"question": "Stylish black guy shows nerd how to spend less time online and get a girlfriend.",
"answer": "The Matrix",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "flocci_naucci",
"upvotes": "1359",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/dvc3uy/stylish_black_guy_shows_nerd_how_to_spend_less/"
},
{
"question": "Driver wrecks Ford.",
"answer": "Ferrari",
"category": "Drama",
"author": "FoX_MoLdY",
"upvotes": "1315",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/8ow2ws/driver_wrecks_ford/"
},
{
"question": "A retired Olympian is harassed by a telekinetic monster.",
"answer": "Carrie",
"category": "Horror",
"author": "Dilarinee",
"upvotes": "1150",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/edn139/a_retired_olympian_is_harassed_by_a_telekinetic/"
},
{
"question": "Man murders dozens of locals by bombing their homes, then adds insult to injury by returning with more (and better) weapons to murder more of them. He comes clean by the end of the film.",
"answer": "Avengers: Age of Ultron",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "[deleted]",
"upvotes": "1124",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/dn1pdn/man_murders_dozens_of_locals_by_bombing_their/"
},
{
"question": "A school boy constantly gets a free pass for his rule breaking because his gay principle takes a liking to him",
"answer": "Harry Potter",
"category": "Fantasy",
"author": "[deleted]",
"upvotes": "1095",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/e600r8/a_school_boy_constantly_gets_a_free_pass_for_his/"
},
{
"question": "Man tries to buy a sculpture with his dad’s old stuff, but fails when his sister is caught crossdressing",
"answer": "Thor: Ragnarok",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "[deleted]",
"upvotes": "1098",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/d27ujz/man_tries_to_buy_a_sculpture_with_his_dads_old/"
},
{
"question": "An overweight chef slaughters a snow leopard because his turtle died",
"answer": "Kung Fu Panda",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "user7526",
"upvotes": "1055",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/iduahe/an_overweight_chef_slaughters_a_snow_leopard/"
},
{
"question": "A blonde woman named Elsa with Germanic origins has a famous scene where the phrase “Let it go” is uttered.",
"answer": "Frozen",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "[deleted]",
"upvotes": "1028",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/fh5yv3/a_blonde_woman_named_elsa_with_germanic_origins/"
},
{
"question": "Rich kid leaves home due to abusive uncle, gets adopted by nihilistic gay couple.",
"answer": "Batman Begins",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "Cye_sonofAphrodite",
"upvotes": "1028",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/cgvs8t/rich_kid_leaves_home_due_to_abusive_uncle_gets/"
},
{
"question": "Dude sleeps with all of his employees",
"answer": "Inception",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "Iron_Nightingale",
"upvotes": "984",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/1hz8b22/dude_sleeps_with_all_of_his_employees/"
},
{
"question": "A weeb, 30s movie fan, ballerina, fat guy, cartoon, and middle schooler walk into a garage.",
"answer": "Avengers: Endgame",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "Pizzamaster199",
"upvotes": "954",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/doykrl/a_weeb_30s_movie_fan_ballerina_fat_guy_cartoon/"
},
{
"question": "Dancing is banned, but some teens do it anyway.",
"answer": "Footloose",
"category": "Drama",
"author": "Actual-Astronaut-604",
"upvotes": "943",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/1em2s71/dancing_is_banned_but_some_teens_do_it_anyway/"
},
{
"question": "A group of midgets go on a hike to get rid of jewelry.",
"answer": "The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring",
"category": "Fantasy",
"author": "[deleted]",
"upvotes": "935",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/9een34/a_group_of_midgets_go_on_a_hike_to_get_rid_of/"
},
{
"question": "A cowboy and his dog and 2 teens blow up their asthmatic father’s office",
"answer": "Star Wars: Episode IV - A New Hope",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "B0b4_F3tt",
"upvotes": "936",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/dodt5f/a_cowboy_and_his_dog_and_2_teens_blow_up_their/"
},
{
"question": "A father is widowed when a serial killer cannibalizes his wife and most of his children. Months later, after losing his last, disabled son due to a boating incident at sea, a mentally-challenged woman is his only hope to finding him.",
"answer": "Finding Nemo",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "jkk45k3jkl534l",
"upvotes": "899",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/9etmuz/a_father_is_widowed_when_a_serial_killer/"
},
{
"question": "A group of schoolteachers take their new friend to beat up a Holocaust survivor and his buddies",
"answer": "X-Men",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "Someoneoverthere42",
"upvotes": "888",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/ijcsxb/a_group_of_schoolteachers_take_their_new_friend/"
},
{
"question": "A failed retired old white man teaches a promising black highschooler how to be like him",
"answer": "Finding Forrester",
"category": "Drama",
"author": "MYZS",
"upvotes": "881",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/dvpxti/a_failed_retired_old_white_man_teaches_a/"
},
{
"question": "This 2001 movie can be summarized as “put that thing back where it came from, or so help me!”",
"answer": "Monsters, Inc.",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "[deleted]",
"upvotes": "878",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/i77qt5/this_2001_movie_can_be_summarized_as_put_that/"
},
{
"question": "The hero only wins because he saved before the final boss.",
"answer": "Edge of Tomorrow",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "[deleted]",
"upvotes": "867",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/ee62tr/the_hero_only_wins_because_he_saved_before_the/"
},
{
"question": "The town's most eligible bachelor gets turned down by a girl who's into furries, so he tries to kill her new boyfriend.",
"answer": "Beauty and the Beast",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "keirmeister",
"upvotes": "858",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/e2p2pv/the_towns_most_eligible_bachelor_gets_turned_down/"
},
{
"question": "A gang beats up a man of colour for trying to improve everyone’s lives",
"answer": "Black Panther",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "R3tr0M3m3s",
"upvotes": "819",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/f8w266/a_gang_beats_up_a_man_of_colour_for_trying_to/"
},
{
"question": "Popular jock has anger issues, drops out from school, marries his high school girlfriend and becomes a cop",
"answer": "The Incredibles",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "user7526",
"upvotes": "823",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/hsvcgb/popular_jock_has_anger_issues_drops_out_from/"
},
{
"question": "Man finally gets head from his wife while a black guy watches",
"answer": "Up",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "[deleted]",
"upvotes": "808",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/eqzmzw/man_finally_gets_head_from_his_wife_while_a_black/"
},
{
"question": ".dlrow eht fo dne eht tneverp ot smia noitarepo terceS",
"answer": "Tenet",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "CheesyObserver",
"upvotes": "806",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/iffc3w/dlrow_eht_fo_dne_eht_tneverp_ot_smia_noitarepo/"
},
{
"question": "There's a vehicle that has to 'speed' around a city, keeping its 'speed' over fifty, and if its 'speed' drops, it will explode. I think it was called 'The Vehicle That Couldn't Slow Down?'",
"answer": "Speed",
"category": "Action",
"author": "mercutio48",
"upvotes": "801",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/1k92uoq/theres_a_vehicle_that_has_to_speed_around_a_city/"
},
{
"question": "12 year old kid breaks into kids homes after the parents leave then proceeds to give the kids “magic dust” that makes the go high as a kite, then he kidnaps them and brings them to a place where they will never grow up filled with murders and racist furries.",
"answer": "Peter Pan",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "jepedo-just-jepedo",
"upvotes": "799",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/e1hb4i/12_year_old_kid_breaks_into_kids_homes_after_the/"
},
{
"question": "Everyone tries to keep a single dad from snapping.",
"answer": "Avengers: Infinity War",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "RedHood000",
"upvotes": "798",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/9do6f9/everyone_tries_to_keep_a_single_dad_from_snapping/"
},
{
"question": "4 New Yorkers get stranded on a tropical island and one of them tries to turn it into a donner party when he gets high and has a really bad case of the munchies",
"answer": "Lord of the Flies",
"category": "Drama",
"author": "LordWeaselton",
"upvotes": "788",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/eli16h/4_new_yorkers_get_stranded_on_a_tropical_island/"
},
{
"question": "Middle-Aged Environmentalist Tries to Collect Colorful Rocks but is Challenged by Men with Facial Hair",
"answer": "Avengers: Infinity War",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "ForkMinus1",
"upvotes": "766",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/8g518k/middleaged_environmentalist_tries_to_collect/"
},
{
"question": "Man is dying, so he becomes an alcoholic and spirals until he saves himself. Another guy wants a bird.",
"answer": "Iron Man",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "StormfistMusic",
"upvotes": "759",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/du81mx/man_is_dying_so_he_becomes_an_alcoholic_and/"
},
{
"question": "He skips his eye exam, destroys the office, delivers a baby, receives a royal last will and testament, smashes up a jewelry store, and finally kills a dude over his snack. Bot bad for a first day on the job.",
"answer": "Spider-Man 2",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "BaconConnoisseur",
"upvotes": "752",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/duwgw6/he_skips_his_eye_exam_destroys_the_office/"
},
{
"question": "32yo teenager supports elderly parental figure by selling photos of self in skin-tight clothing.",
"answer": "Spider-Man: Homecoming",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "MightGetFiredIDK",
"upvotes": "755",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/g627ib/32yo_teenager_supports_elderly_parental_figure_by/"
},
{
"question": "After being released from prison, man laments lost time while immediately seeking revenge. Also, there’s a… frog?",
"answer": "Magnolia",
"category": "Drama",
"author": "TheDorkKnight53",
"upvotes": "750",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/1ejalko/after_being_released_from_prison_man_laments_lost/"
},
{
"question": "Take your son to work day ends with the dad killing his boss",
"answer": "Star Wars: Episode VI - Return of the Jedi",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "acoyne1",
"upvotes": "743",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/e88t4x/take_your_son_to_work_day_ends_with_the_dad/"
},
{
"question": "Religious cult uses a child soldier to blow up a corporation's headquarters to so they can restore the monarchy",
"answer": "Star Wars: Episode IV - A New Hope",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "SploonTheDude",
"upvotes": "740",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/dwfsk4/religious_cult_uses_a_child_soldier_to_blow_up_a/"
},
{
"question": "Man isn't qualified for the job, but he needs it nevertheless, so he seals a pact with a strange creature to grant him the power to get through the challenges ahead.",
"answer": "Spirited Away",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "[deleted]",
"upvotes": "739",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/jap7a9/man_isnt_qualified_for_the_job_but_he_needs_it/"
},
{
"question": "A father wants his reluctant son to help in the family business. Eventually the son gives his dad a hand.",
"answer": "Star Wars: Episode V - The Empire Strikes Back",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "[deleted]",
"upvotes": "735",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/j8zw72/a_father_wants_his_reluctant_son_to_help_in_the/"
},
{
"question": "Put that thing back where it came from or so help me.",
"answer": "Monsters, Inc.",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "Nova_Saibrock",
"upvotes": "721",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/duj54j/put_that_thing_back_where_it_came_from_or_so_help/"
},
{
"question": "The town thinks the old-fashioned sheriff murdered the mysterious modern stranger. The sheriff and the newcomer have to put aside their differences when they’re kidnapped by a murderous sociopath.",
"answer": "Toy Story 3",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "why___not___zoidberg",
"upvotes": "721",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/e5r6eb/the_town_thinks_the_oldfashioned_sheriff_murdered/"
},
{
"question": "Everyone tries the ice bucket challenge",
"answer": "Frozen",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "Clever_Username06",
"upvotes": "715",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/e4jx8l/everyone_tries_the_ice_bucket_challenge/"
},
{
"question": "Two wizards get into a fight. One wizard decides to get high, and leaves the other one to light up alone.",
"answer": "The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers",
"category": "Fantasy",
"author": "TheLovingNightmare",
"upvotes": "712",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/erquue/two_wizards_get_into_a_fight_one_wizard_decides/"
},
{
"question": "Man has his inner voice surgically removed, gives it to a 60 year old obsessed with a little girl",
"answer": "Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind",
"category": "Drama",
"author": "Eran-of-Arcadia",
"upvotes": "710",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/gxrati/man_has_his_inner_voice_surgically_removed_gives/"
},
{
"question": "Guy has house party, robs a crackhead, breaks into a massive vault, and fights a bunch of rival gangs.",
"answer": "Black Panther",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "jsilvy",
"upvotes": "706",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/f4san2/guy_has_house_party_robs_a_crackhead_breaks_into/"
},
{
"question": "After his big sister breaks his favorite toy, an orphaned boy runs away to stay with a friend. After a few weeks, he returns to get revenge and with his friend’s help he kills his sister’s dog and burns down their home with her still inside.",
"answer": "Toy Story",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "Thegingerkid01",
"upvotes": "696",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/8kqbs4/after_his_big_sister_breaks_his_favorite_toy_an/"
},
{
"question": "Guy is trained in the use of fingers by older woman",
"answer": "Avatar",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "[deleted]",
"upvotes": "687",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/cwmxb2/guy_is_trained_in_the_use_of_fingers_by_older/"
},
{
"question": "It's like if that Kanye song was about babies.",
"answer": "Boss Baby",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "Quirky-Reputation-89",
"upvotes": "683",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/1iork1k/its_like_if_that_kanye_song_was_about_babies/"
},
{
"question": "Two mothers, black and white, fight over the black's reproductive rights.",
"answer": "Get Out",
"category": "Horror",
"author": "IntelligentPredator",
"upvotes": "682",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/dy3wyi/two_mothers_black_and_white_fight_over_the_blacks/"
},
{
"question": "Child gets abused for the first 10 years of his life then gets kidnapped by a big bearded man on his 11th birthday",
"answer": "Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone",
"category": "Fantasy",
"author": "[deleted]",
"upvotes": "684",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/9eolj4/child_gets_abused_for_the_first_10_years_of_his/"
},
{
"question": "A teenage girl marries a foot fetishist to escape her abusive family.",
"answer": "Aladdin",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "SleepingIsUnderrated",
"upvotes": "673",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/iv3gfr/a_teenage_girl_marries_a_foot_fetishist_to_escape/"
},
{
"question": "2 guys 1 cup",
"answer": "Dumb and Dumber",
"category": "Comedy",
"author": "dangergypsy",
"upvotes": "659",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/iis9mb/2_guys_1_cup/"
},
{
"question": "People sleeping on an international flight. Then they get off the plane, uneventfully.",
"answer": "Inception",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "Patient-Principle",
"upvotes": "654",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/ey3hy3/people_sleeping_on_an_international_flight_then/"
},
{
"question": "A kid announces and sings to the whole world that he can't wait for his father to be dead so he can replace him as the leader of their community",
"answer": "The Lion King",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "jrfnavarro",
"upvotes": "652",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/jr65ws/a_kid_announces_and_sings_to_the_whole_world_that/"
},
{
"question": "My dad is dead.. wait no he's not. Yes he is. No he's not. Hol up my friend is my dad.",
"answer": "The Lion King",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "garbonzobean22",
"upvotes": "649",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/j5hyfa/my_dad_is_dead_wait_no_hes_not_yes_he_is_no_hes/"
},
{
"question": "Orphan likes to dress up at night, tie and punish naughty boys",
"answer": "Batman Begins",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "MrCastielPT",
"upvotes": "653",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/i90xmf/orphan_likes_to_dress_up_at_night_tie_and_punish/"
},
{
"question": "A boy drugs his grandmother and enlists an african tribe to tie him up and squeeze all of the fluid out of him so that he can pay off a debt to a construction development company that wants to evict him.",
"answer": "Willy Wonka & the Chocolate Factory",
"category": "Family",
"author": "Aggressive_Muffin",
"upvotes": "648",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/eu2g0q/a_boy_drugs_his_grandmother_and_enlists_an/"
},
{
"question": "Grandpa wants to make a fortune out of mosquitos",
"answer": "Jurassic Park",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "PARhymE",
"upvotes": "645",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/dth4rg/grandpa_wants_to_make_a_fortune_out_of_mosquitos/"
},
{
"question": "Declared public menace kidnaps child and murders elderly celebrity just to fulfill a fantasy involving a dead woman",
"answer": "Up",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "ricarleite1",
"upvotes": "647",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/d6uflo/declared_public_menace_kidnaps_child_and_murders/"
},
{
"question": "The whole family has to move because of dad’s job. Everything goes horribly wrong, dad dies and teen son ends up lost and addicted to drugs. But he literally meets the girl of his dreams. ",
"answer": "Finding Nemo",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "[deleted]",
"upvotes": "640",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/1hf88vp/the_whole_family_has_to_move_because_of_dads_job/"
},
{
"question": "Lonely guy kills a family of european immigrants because he saw one of them smash his favourite bich",
"answer": "John Wick",
"category": "Action",
"author": "Triktastic",
"upvotes": "630",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/f1s9hl/lonely_guy_kills_a_family_of_european_immigrants/"
},
{
"question": "Autistic man raised by Christian-adjacent cult falls in love with a woman too attractive to be working in a dept. store. ",
"answer": "Napoleon Dynamite",
"category": "Comedy",
"author": "DueSupport2703",
"upvotes": "628",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/1hm8whh/autistic_man_raised_by_christianadjacent_cult/"
},
{
"question": "Some nerd kisses his sister and fights his dad.",
"answer": "Star Wars: Episode V - The Empire Strikes Back",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "throwawaybyebye17",
"upvotes": "625",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/9edboo/some_nerd_kisses_his_sister_and_fights_his_dad/"
},
{
"question": "Girl gets engaged to the first guy she meets but then falls for another guy she meets later that day.",
"answer": "Frozen",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "TisMeBeinMe",
"upvotes": "621",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/hunkgk/girl_gets_engaged_to_the_first_guy_she_meets_but/"
},
{
"question": "European sports star asks out pretty but nerdy 14 year old",
"answer": "Beauty and the Beast",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "TheQcumber69",
"upvotes": "628",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/egr722/european_sports_star_asks_out_pretty_but_nerdy_14/"
},
{
"question": "[Series] Two boys build stuff while their pet bullies a pharmacist",
"answer": "Phineas and Ferb",
"category": "TV",
"author": "AnthonyTheIntrovert",
"upvotes": "626",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/hdw4t3/series_two_boys_build_stuff_while_their_pet/"
},
{
"question": "Girl uses 100% of her brain to get adopted by a better parent.",
"answer": "Lucy",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "Eyes_of_The_Lord",
"upvotes": "618",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/heggkq/girl_uses_100_of_her_brain_to_get_adopted_by_a/"
},
{
"question": "A man is able to see the future but everybody ridicules him instead of helping, resulting in the death of his wife",
"answer": "The Dead Zone",
"category": "Thriller",
"author": "ScheidNation21",
"upvotes": "619",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/gm8qmr/a_man_is_able_to_see_the_future_but_everybody/"
},
{
"question": "Jesus is a furry and decides to give power to a bunch of kids.",
"answer": "The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe",
"category": "Fantasy",
"author": "jsilvy",
"upvotes": "616",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/fq0pxd/jesus_is_a_furry_and_decides_to_give_power_to_a/"
},
{
"question": "01001101 01101111 01100001 01101110 01100001 00100000 01100010 01110101 01110100 00100000 01001101 01100101 01111000 01101001 01100011 01100001 01101110 00100000",
"answer": "Moana but Mexican",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "thogolicious",
"upvotes": "608",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/f9t6y3/01001101_01101111_01100001_01101110_01100001/"
},
{
"question": "A ship tragically sinks in this one. An upper class girl meets a lower class boy on a maiden journey. She’s engaged to a rich jerk; he’s traveling with his easygoing buddy. When things go wrong, they’re exposed to frigid conditions. She survives—her heart will go on.",
"answer": "Titanic",
"category": "Drama",
"author": "HeftyButton",
"upvotes": "609",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/1lmv3cb/a_ship_tragically_sinks_in_this_one_an_upper/"
},
{
"question": "A creepy old man finally achieves his goal of being able to touch a 14 year old boy",
"answer": "The Sixth Sense",
"category": "Thriller",
"author": "Goodzon",
"upvotes": "610",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/ipwye1/a_creepy_old_man_finally_achieves_his_goal_of/"
},
{
"question": "A monarch illegally breaks into another nation, kidnaps their leader and steals their identity, wreaks havoc on their country and survives an assassination attempt, and in the end learns the lesson that you should never change and you should only stay with your own kind.",
"answer": "The Little Mermaid",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "[deleted]",
"upvotes": "602",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/j49k3t/a_monarch_illegally_breaks_into_another_nation/"
},
{
"question": "A group of deformed teenagers battle a gang of body parts led by a piece of office equipment.",
"answer": "Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles",
"category": "Action",
"author": "boy_yeets_world",
"upvotes": "602",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/fnl9ze/a_bunch_of_deformed_teenagers_battle_a_gang_of/"
},
{
"question": "This movie is one part Tom and Jerry, one part Harry Potter, and one part foot fetish",
"answer": "Ratatouille",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "[deleted]",
"upvotes": "600",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/f0sldh/this_movie_is_one_part_tom_and_jerry_one_part/"
},
{
"question": "The president of China searches for a friend's missing body part while slowly starving to death",
"answer": "Cast Away",
"category": "Drama",
"author": "Omboreas",
"upvotes": "596",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/ja7kwg/the_president_of_china_searches_for_a_friends/"
},
{
"question": "How to Get Good at Explaining Films Badly: A Guide",
"answer": "N/A",
"category": "Meta",
"author": "Rephath",
"upvotes": "601",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/1f171l8/how_to_get_good_at_explaining_films_badly_a_guide/"
},
{
"question": "A survival of the fittest contest inside a sweatshop, winner gets the sweatshop",
"answer": "Squid Game",
"category": "Thriller",
"author": "ziv_hamagniv",
"upvotes": "596",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/j1wome/a_survival_of_the_fittest_contest_inside_a/"
},
{
"question": "Man can make his penis bigger whenever he wants",
"answer": "Ant-Man",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "justjay07",
"upvotes": "597",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/j9datv/man_can_make_his_penis_bigger_whenever_he_wants/"
},
{
"question": "Man has everything but loses his wife. Travels to the future only to be murdered by her.",
"answer": "The Time Traveler's Wife",
"category": "Drama",
"author": "Jesus_for_profit",
"upvotes": "587",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/imqtkg/man_has_everything_but_loses_his_wife_travels_to/"
},
{
"question": "It takes 63 minutes for the movie’s title to actually start",
"answer": "2001: A Space Odyssey",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "Blastspark01",
"upvotes": "588",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/fc2ljr/it_takes_63_minutes_for_the_movies_title_to/"
},
{
"question": "So it turns out there's this world with witches and wizards and magic and stuff right along side our world. Main character grew up without knowing they were a part of it. Trains to use magic and fly on fancy modern looking brooms. Eventually defeats the bad dude with a creepy grey-skinned face.",
"answer": "Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone",
"category": "Fantasy",
"author": "Anon-Ymous929",
"upvotes": "585",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/jgpiqv/so_it_turns_out_theres_this_world_with_witches/"
},
{
"question": "So there's this guy, and he just doesn't like babies, and his girlfriend really wants to change his mind so they take a vacation to a tropical island where she makes him spend the day with these two kids they met that took a liking to him.",
"answer": "Lilo & Stitch",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "lallapalalable",
"upvotes": "585",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/is2uhn/so_theres_this_guy_and_he_just_doesnt_like_babies/"
},
{
"question": "[Meta] Your post in ExplainAFilmPlotBadly should actually be explaining the plot.",
"answer": "N/A",
"category": "Meta",
"author": "SciFiXhi",
"upvotes": "585",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/1kgy6o8/meta_your_post_in_explainafilmplotbadly_should/"
},
{
"question": "[META] Stop erasing your guesses",
"answer": "N/A",
"category": "Meta",
"author": "Pope_Cerebus",
"upvotes": "577",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/ioig96/meta_stop_erasing_your_guesses/"
},
{
"question": "Coloured man is segregated from society until he takes down a ruthless dictator and saves the girl",
"answer": "Shrek",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "R3tr0M3m3s",
"upvotes": "576",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/h0y0q9/coloured_man_is_segregated_from_society_until_he/"
},
{
"question": "Socially isolating children creates adults who make poor decisions",
"answer": "Frozen",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "buzz1627",
"upvotes": "572",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/h7pkev/socially_isolating_children_creates_adults_who/"
},
{
"question": "A professional athlete develops Stockholm syndrome after the residents of a small town holds him against his will",
"answer": "Cars",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "doctormisterio19",
"upvotes": "567",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/a4mrt4/a_professional_athlete_develops_stockholm/"
},
{
"question": "[META] The Batman Rule.",
"answer": "N/A",
"category": "Meta",
"author": "timeshaper",
"upvotes": "569",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/lg6g0j/meta_the_batman_rule/"
},
{
"question": "A young mother dies of AIDS after encouraging a friend's running career",
"answer": "Forrest Gump",
"category": "Drama",
"author": "tasteslikechimp",
"upvotes": "564",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/dsjsk3/a_young_mother_dies_of_aids_after_encouraging_a/"
},
{
"question": "Old man kidnaps Asian kid, kills celebrity.",
"answer": "Gran Torino",
"category": "Drama",
"author": "AranaesReddit",
"upvotes": "559",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/jmrs0h/old_man_kidnaps_asian_kid_kills_celebrity/"
},
{
"question": "Man gets his lifetime crush killed, spends rest of his life plotting to save her son’s life",
"answer": "Harry Potter series",
"category": "Fantasy",
"author": "cheesybread336",
"upvotes": "560",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/ih9sgh/man_gets_his_lifetime_crush_killed_spends_rest_of/"
},
{
"question": "Two naked factory workers run from the authorities after kidnapping a kid.",
"answer": "Terminator 2: Judgment Day",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "RikCooper",
"upvotes": "561",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/g258f6/two_naked_factory_workers_run_from_the/"
},
{
"question": "Old man mourning the loss of his wife abducts a small asian boy",
"answer": "Gran Torino",
"category": "Drama",
"author": "SimplyZea",
"upvotes": "558",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/hjyjwp/old_man_mourning_the_loss_of_his_wife_abducts_a/"
},
{
"question": "Boy gets psychologically tortured until he learns to beat something with sticks correctly",
"answer": "Whiplash",
"category": "Drama",
"author": "mydogs7thnipple",
"upvotes": "560",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/dtuyl5/boy_gets_psychologically_tortured_until_he_learns/"
},
{
"question": "A gang comes together to bully the little brother of one of them",
"answer": "Avengers: Endgame",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "Darhty",
"upvotes": "560",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/hx2pfj/a_gang_comes_together_to_bully_the_little_brother/"
},
{
"question": "Man denied Promotion; Massaceres children.",
"answer": "Star Wars: Episode III - Revenge of the Sith",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "Xx_k4ng4r00_xX",
"upvotes": "557",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/9jgwy6/man_denied_promotion_massaceres_children/"
},
{
"question": "A guy’s wife tries going topless. It causes problems for them.",
"answer": "Jaws",
"category": "Thriller",
"author": "HeftyButton",
"upvotes": "557",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/1jquilh/a_guys_wife_tries_going_topless_it_causes/"
},
{
"question": "A man with a drinking problem gets a chance to fly a plane again. He crashes, likely killing thousands, but his kids are still proud of him.",
"answer": "Independence Day",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "C4dfael",
"upvotes": "550",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/1i62ygz/a_man_with_a_drinking_problem_gets_a_chance_to/"
},
{
"question": "A hard working prodigy is denied a legendary promotion, punished for displaying his disapproval, only to have that position given to a complete greenhorn",
"answer": "Star Wars: Episode III - Revenge of the Sith",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "[deleted]",
"upvotes": "546",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/gye4d8/a_hard_working_prodigy_is_denied_a_legendary/"
},
{
"question": "A twist! And then lesbian sex. And then another twist! And then lesbian sex. And then another twist! And end with some lesbian text.",
"answer": "Mulholland Drive",
"category": "Drama",
"author": "[deleted]",
"upvotes": "547",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/ejx0eo/a_twist_and_then_lesbian_sex_and_then_another/"
},
{
"question": "A creature with tentacles sends an even bigger creature with tentacles to suck on people. And this is not Japanese porn",
"answer": "Stranger Things",
"category": "TV",
"author": "[deleted]",
"upvotes": "540",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/e49bz9/a_creature_with_tentacles_sends_an_even_bigger/"
},
{
"question": "Two kids become friends and then take a shower together",
"answer": "E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "Paw_s",
"upvotes": "547",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/9ne1fd/two_kids_become_friends_and_then_take_a_shower/"
},
{
"question": "Professor X is a real piece of shit in this movie.",
"answer": "Logan",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "Childish_Cambino2187",
"upvotes": "546",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/geqjnt/professor_x_is_a_real_piece_of_shit_in_this_movie/"
},
{
"question": "Space Jesus roasts his best friend",
"answer": "Star Wars: Episode III - Revenge of the Sith",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "Roku-Hanmar",
"upvotes": "543",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/ibehat/space_jesus_roasts_his_best_friend/"
},
{
"question": "Rock brings rock to a rock.",
"answer": "Moana",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "curlyvltr",
"upvotes": "536",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/ivi63z/rock_brings_rock_to_a_rock/"
},
{
"question": "Young girl takes the last name of her hard-core crush. Almost gets killed because of it",
"answer": "Twilight",
"category": "Fantasy",
"author": "sc",
"upvotes": "540",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/hi38ct/young_girl_takes_the_last_name_of_her_hardcore/"
},
{
"question": "META: Film plot insta-solver!",
"answer": "N/A",
"category": "Meta",
"author": "DramaGuy23",
"upvotes": "538",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/dp89ja/meta_film_plot_instasolver/"
},
{
"question": "Evil guy returns from the dead to conquer the world with copy/paste",
"answer": "The Mummy",
"category": "Adventure",
"author": "ImKindaWrong",
"upvotes": "485",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/hg79uu/evil_guy_returns_from_the_dead_to_conquer_the/"
},
{
"question": "A sweet old man is kidnapped from his hometown, imprisoned by a crazed gambler, so that a tall emo guy can steal his career.",
"answer": "Ratatouille",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "[deleted]",
"upvotes": "495",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/e6hd0w/a_sweet_old_man_is_kidnapped_from_his_hometown/"
},
{
"question": "A rat is the real hero of this story.",
"answer": "Ratatouille",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "MissBarker93",
"upvotes": "487",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/dx6683/a_rat_is_the_real_hero_of_this_story/"
},
{
"question": "A guy blows up some buildings because he couldn't sleep.",
"answer": "Fight Club",
"category": "Drama",
"author": "ya_boy_mate",
"upvotes": "491",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/iyw4yt/a_guy_blows_up_some_buildings_because_he_couldnt/"
},
{
"question": "Short men taunt kids due to their misfortune",
"answer": "Charlie and the Chocolate Factory",
"category": "Family",
"author": "Drago0980",
"upvotes": "482",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/gz8i8r/short_men_taunt_kids_due_to_their_misfortune/"
},
{
"question": "Two inseparable friends quit their job to take on the world with a band of misfits.",
"answer": "Guardians of the Galaxy",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "Agorafiliax",
"upvotes": "481",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/ha0sa6/two_inseparable_friends_quit_their_job_to_take_on/"
},
{
"question": "Unemployed lady hangs Christmas lights and talks to herself on the phone hoping her child will come back..",
"answer": "Home Alone",
"category": "Comedy",
"author": "MLScarletHeart",
"upvotes": "487",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/dzh4m3/unemployed_lady_hangs_christmas_lights_and_talks/"
},
{
"question": "Elderly woman tells strangers about her past sexual escapades, destroys valuable heirlooms.",
"answer": "Titanic",
"category": "Drama",
"author": "[deleted]",
"upvotes": "485",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/hnzous/elderly_woman_tells_strangers_about_her_past/"
},
{
"question": "We really need an r/ExplainABookPlotBadly. I can't make it because I don't have enough karma.",
"answer": "N/A",
"category": "Meta",
"author": "xd_Underated",
"upvotes": "481",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/cvuu6k/we_really_need_an_rexplainabookplotbadly_i_cant/"
},
{
"question": "Man pisses off his entire family over the course of one night and accidentally endangers the livelihood of the only person who isn't pissed at him.",
"answer": "Home Alone",
"category": "Comedy",
"author": "[deleted]",
"upvotes": "482",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/gms4vq/man_pisses_off_his_entire_family_over_the_course/"
},
{
"question": "This dogs movie isn’t even about dogs",
"answer": "Reservoir Dogs",
"category": "Crime",
"author": "Skystalker512",
"upvotes": "486",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/fhzx17/this_dogs_movie_isnt_even_about_dogs/"
},
{
"question": "Adam Sandler is horribly miscast in a movie where he plays himself.",
"answer": "Uncut Gems",
"category": "Drama",
"author": "Tijnenzer",
"upvotes": "483",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/gumeu1/adam_sandler_is_horri..."
},
{
"question": "abandoned child tortures two men",
"answer": "Home Alone",
"category": "Comedy",
"author": "SpieWonder",
"upvotes": "242",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/9f7p8b/abandoned_child_tortures_two_men/"
},
{
"question": "Women are held in a concentration camp where they are beheaded if they are unable to give birth. They have tried escaping, but when a circus performer from another country finds the camp, they all realize he can help the women escape.",
"answer": "Water for Elephants",
"category": "Drama",
"author": "Zant6304",
"upvotes": "245",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/olw4mm/women_are_held_in_a_concentration_camp_where_they/"
},
{
"question": "Girl's memories live rent-free in his head.",
"answer": "Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind",
"category": "Drama",
"author": "[deleted]",
"upvotes": "244",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/lbn51t/girls_memories_live_rentfree_in_his_head/"
},
{
"question": "Aliens fight against property development",
"answer": "Avatar",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "dailysunshineKO",
"upvotes": "246",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/l1cmai/aliens_fight_against_property_development/"
},
{
"question": "25 years later and people still accuse Disney of ripping this off.",
"answer": "Kimba the White Lion",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "MissBarker93",
"upvotes": "242",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/d45mzs/25_years_later_and_people_still_accuse_disney_of/"
},
{
"question": "Jeff fcking Goldblum.",
"answer": "The Fly",
"category": "Horror",
"author": "xXYoProMamaXx",
"upvotes": "244",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/d0em8x/jeff_fcking_goldblum/"
},
{
"question": "Two guys beat the crap out of each other for no reason until their mommies make them stop",
"answer": "Batman v Superman: Dawn of Justice",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "killa5abi",
"upvotes": "241",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/blzzki/two_guys_beat_the_crap_out_of_each_other_for_no/"
},
{
"question": "A man races to create a bomb that will change history regarding the fight against Nazi Germany. He assembles a team. The bomb is dropped and it’s a direct hit. He’s publicly praised but feels regret in the aftermath. He’s dragged in front of a hearing where his character is questioned.",
"answer": "Oppenheimer",
"category": "Drama",
"author": "HeftyButton",
"upvotes": "240",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/1mfsldv/a_man_races_to_create_a_bomb_that_will_change/"
},
{
"question": "This sequel is just the first one again, but they changed the sex of the killer.",
"answer": "Scream 2",
"category": "Horror",
"author": "CuddlesTom",
"upvotes": "241",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/1kpzo37/this_sequel_is_just_the_first_one_again_but_they/"
},
{
"question": "A veteran returns home only to find his family dead and a corrupt politician has seized all his property. Left with no other options, he spends his time camping in the woods with his friends.",
"answer": "Rambo: First Blood",
"category": "Action",
"author": "Mr_Mike013",
"upvotes": "241",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/1hw4s0u/a_veteran_returns_home_only_to_find_his_family/"
},
{
"question": "Guy has a mental breakdown when he realizes his whole identity was a lie while his jealous predecessor tries to escape a torture chamber their both trapped in",
"answer": "Spider-Man: No Way Home",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "RedRanger_27",
"upvotes": "238",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/oq0xj4/guy_has_a_mental_breakdown_when_he_realizes_his/"
},
{
"question": "Taught that he was an outcast due to his skin colour as a child, a man wreaks havoc in his community",
"answer": "Shrek",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "nagitoe_",
"upvotes": "239",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/nneytu/taught_that_he_was_an_outcast_due_to_his_skin/"
},
{
"question": "Society is shaken when a caged animal shows that it can talk.",
"answer": "Planet of the Apes",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "TheUnvanquishable",
"upvotes": "244",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/nm2sxu/society_is_shaken_when_a_caged_animal_shows_that/"
},
{
"question": "Man gets attacked by ancient stuff then gets beat up by old men",
"answer": "Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull",
"category": "Adventure",
"author": "Exoticbutters5834",
"upvotes": "241",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/mdcub7/man_gets_attacked_by_ancient_stuff_then_gets_beat/"
},
{
"question": "Easy",
"answer": "The Big Lebowski",
"category": "Comedy",
"author": "8609936w0hzkf",
"upvotes": "240",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/hm6jue/easy/"
},
{
"question": "112 year old guy falls in love with a 14 year old girl and together they fight against an oppressive monarchy",
"answer": "Twilight",
"category": "Fantasy",
"author": "Sermest2",
"upvotes": "243",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/adnhvv/112_year_old_guy_falls_in_love_with_a_14_year_old/"
},
{
"question": "A group of men represented by colors suspect that there is an impostor among them.",
"answer": "Reservoir Dogs",
"category": "Crime",
"author": "GodzillaZERONE",
"upvotes": "242",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/mr2lns/a_group_of_men_represented_by_colors_suspect_that/"
},
{
"question": "Boy gets kidnapped after his mum is killed by a bad guy",
"answer": "The Lion King",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "ObamaInAToaster21",
"upvotes": "242",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/ld7bfi/boy_gets_kidnapped_after_his_mum_is_killed_by_a/"
},
{
"question": "Farmer eats boiled potatoes and nothing more interesting.",
"answer": "The Martian",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "Ninjaxas",
"upvotes": "241",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/kpd4c6/farmer_eats_boiled_potatoes_and_nothing_more/"
},
{
"question": "Games: The book: the movie.",
"answer": "The Hunger Games",
"category": "Action",
"author": "shirukien",
"upvotes": "238",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/j2b22b/games_the_book_the_movie/"
},
{
"question": "Chicken stows away on boat. Gets kidnapped by pirates. Saves rock.",
"answer": "Moana",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "Whakahoa",
"upvotes": "242",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/fb57zh/chicken_stows_away_on_boat_gets_kidnapped_by/"
},
{
"question": "Creepy looking old man lures teenager into his car",
"answer": "Back to the Future",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "Ethan_ML10",
"upvotes": "239",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/cqhkpx/creepy_looking_old_man_lures_teenager_into_his_car/"
},
{
"question": "A bunch of people with extra chromosomes attack a rock with a big gun",
"answer": "Star Wars: Episode VI - Return of the Jedi",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "Doot_Slayer42069",
"upvotes": "240",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/lon05y/a_bunch_of_people_with_extra_chromosomes_attack_a/"
},
{
"question": "Our heroes band together and travel to unknown lands to stop an evil megalomaniac from going power mad over his collection of glowing rocks",
"answer": "Avengers: Infinity War",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "gro330",
"upvotes": "242",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/b2gl6l/our_heroes_band_together_and_travel_to_unknown/"
},
{
"question": "Some metal is unintentionally put through the Wash; everyone gets upset ",
"answer": "Captain America: The Winter Soldier",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "Reddituser0346",
"upvotes": "238",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/1fr57jz/some_metal_is_unintentionally_put_through_the/"
},
{
"question": "Guy meets 15-year-old and is arrested. After he escapes, he rubs one out. Then his nemesis rubs one out.",
"answer": "Scott Pilgrim vs. the World",
"category": "Comedy",
"author": "Gogo726",
"upvotes": "242",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/sc7avq/guy_meets_15yearold_and_is_arrested_after_he/"
},
{
"question": "A demented old lady stubbornly stays in a dangerous old house, standing in the way of her kind-hearted would-be benefactor and his multi-million dollar development, and is aided by a demonic spirit that has possessed a Volkswagen.",
"answer": "Up",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "TerriblyGentlemanly",
"upvotes": "241",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/mh284a/a_demented_old_lady_stubbornly_stays_in_a/"
},
{
"question": "Guy wins a girl with a green horse",
"answer": "Shrek",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "GymnoJake",
"upvotes": "241",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/fvaorq/guy_wins_a_girl_with_a_green_horse/"
},
{
"question": "It's technically a super hero movie telling the origin story of a Marvel character but it would be abusive to ban me from this sub.",
"answer": "Joker",
"category": "Drama",
"author": "Caeflin",
"upvotes": "242",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/1j91bs7/its_technically_a_super_hero_movie_telling_the/"
},
{
"question": "A boy is so horny he's willing to punch people into coins for his gf",
"answer": "Scott Pilgrim vs. the World",
"category": "Comedy",
"author": "AcceptableAd9043",
"upvotes": "237",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/odfex4/a_boy_is_so_horny_hes_willing_to_punch_people/"
},
{
"question": "Hairy man gets very thirsty waiting for his friends to pick him up",
"answer": "The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers",
"category": "Fantasy",
"author": "CH1CK3NW1N95",
"upvotes": "239",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/nigpi2/hairy_man_gets_very_thirsty_waiting_for_his/"
},
{
"question": "Dude saves a guy from slavery, almost kills him with his selfish goals and then abandons him",
"answer": "Star Wars: Episode IV - A New Hope",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "crazykid080",
"upvotes": "236",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/mrqwct/dude_saves_a_guy_from_slavery_almost_kills_him/"
},
{
"question": "A bunch of illegal aliens fight off the power of Will Smith.",
"answer": "Independence Day",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "xXYoProMamaXx",
"upvotes": "236",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/d00z2j/a_bunch_of_illegal_aliens_fight_off_the_power_of/"
},
{
"question": "Man is tortured under the guise of 'treatment', but damn is he good at math",
"answer": "A Beautiful Mind",
"category": "Drama",
"author": "Killairmanable",
"upvotes": "240",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/ctifgg/man_is_tortured_under_the_guise_of_treatment_but/"
},
{
"question": "4 men use unlicensed particle accelerators to fight a painting.",
"answer": "Ghostbusters",
"category": "Comedy",
"author": "TheRealSilverBlade",
"upvotes": "237",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/c2xhst/4_men_use_unlicensed_particle_accelerators_to/"
},
{
"question": "This movie is also about trying to make this movie.",
"answer": "Birdman",
"category": "Drama",
"author": "BigNimbleyD",
"upvotes": "237",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/dk5bkz/this_movie_is_also_about_trying_to_make_this_movie/"
},
{
"question": "Due to family drama, Goldilocks loses their hair and becomes a space pirate.",
"answer": "Guardians of the Galaxy",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "MurderousUnicorns",
"upvotes": "239",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/bg4bnt/due_to_family_drama_goldilocks_loses_their_hair/"
},
{
"question": "Whiny teenager wants to leave home. Eventually does so and murders millions of law enforcement personnel.",
"answer": "Star Wars: Episode IV - A New Hope",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "bitterhipster",
"upvotes": "237",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/9rszvi/whiny_teenager_wants_to_leave_home_eventually/"
},
{
"question": "It's 106 miles to “Chicago”, they got a full tank of gas, half a pack of cigarettes, it's dark... and they're wearing sunglasses",
"answer": "The Blues Brothers",
"category": "Comedy",
"author": "Life_Wolverine_6830",
"upvotes": "238",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/1hb07sj/its_106_miles_to_chicago_they_got_a_full_tank_of/"
},
{
"question": "British kids take like, 20 years to come out of the closet",
"answer": "The Chronicles of Narnia",
"category": "Fantasy",
"author": "[deleted]",
"upvotes": "235",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/1fhptoz/british_kids_take_like_20_years_to_come_out_of/"
},
{
"question": "A man and his imaginary-but-actually-there friend learn gaslighting is bad even if it's good.",
"answer": "Jojo Rabbit",
"category": "Drama",
"author": "[deleted]",
"upvotes": "237",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/nxskos/a_man_and_his_imaginarybutactuallythere_friend/"
},
{
"question": "Descendant of ancient demon goes to great lengths to resurrect another demon and ultimately makes sure that blood is spilled because of a belief that this will make the sun rise.",
"answer": "Castlevania",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "Traditional_Desk_411",
"upvotes": "240",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/lmlvnv/descendant_of_ancient_demon_goes_to_great_lengths/"
},
{
"question": "(Anime) 10 year old boy enslaves hundreds of animals for his own sick sense of delight; also, he manipulates way too many people of power into giving him free stuff out of nowhere.",
"answer": "Pokémon",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "[deleted]",
"upvotes": "237",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/n0r343/anime_10_year_old_boy_enslaves_hundreds_of/"
},
{
"question": "Guy tries to be fight racism only to find out he is very racist himself",
"answer": "American History X",
"category": "Drama",
"author": "Ninjaxas",
"upvotes": "234",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/mxra85/guy_tries_to_be_fight_racism_only_to_find_out_he/"
},
{
"question": "His relative tells him to buy a house in California, so he does.",
"answer": "Encanto",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "musicman827",
"upvotes": "232",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/ljq5dw/his_relative_tells_him_to_buy_a_house_in/"
},
{
"question": "Special Ed man wins escape room, rest of group doesn't.",
"answer": "Us",
"category": "Horror",
"author": "BrockLee7",
"upvotes": "231",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/dcp2od/special_ed_man_wins_escape_room_rest_of_group/"
},
{
"question": "Man’s shoes won’t come off, builds dangerous machine in an act of retaliation.",
"answer": "Cloudy with a Chance of Meatballs",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "Yeetaroni",
"upvotes": "235",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/czow48/mans_shoes_wont_come_off_builds_dangerous_machine/"
},
{
"question": "Aa trip to Europe is put to a halt when a guy and his friends end up being persecuted by someone who wants their heads.",
"answer": "The Da Vinci Code",
"category": "Thriller",
"author": "AceiteDeOlivas",
"upvotes": "234",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/cd2cee/aa_trip_to_europe_is_put_to_a_halt_when_a_guy_and/"
},
{
"question": "A group of people from different races help someone return a piece of jewellery. But you only see the first 3 hours of it.",
"answer": "The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring",
"category": "Fantasy",
"author": "TheRealSilverBlade",
"upvotes": "233",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/c4cuhk/a_group_of_people_from_different_races_help/"
},
{
"question": "A green creature wants to ruin a holiday for a bunch midgets",
"answer": "How the Grinch Stole Christmas",
"category": "Family",
"author": "Jakiboy1234",
"upvotes": "235",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/9c815k/a_green_creature_wants_to_ruin_a_holiday_for_a/"
},
{
"question": "Multinational team finds a rock and very nearly commits genocide of an ancient people.",
"answer": "Avengers: Endgame",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "rattatatouille",
"upvotes": "233",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/nssx1i/multinational_team_finds_a_rock_and_very_nearly/"
},
{
"question": "Harley Quinn gets the help of Gamora and Ms. Noodle to help save a kingdom from the Full Metal Bitch and Wilson Frisk",
"answer": "Birds of Prey",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "eddmario",
"upvotes": "233",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/di5avt/harley_quinn_gets_the_help_of_gamora_and_ms/"
},
{
"question": "man gets gangbanged for wearing glove",
"answer": "Avengers: Infinity War",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "Spetsnaz_GRU",
"upvotes": "236",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/cjrl5e/man_gets_gangbanged_for_wearing_glove/"
},
{
"question": "After woman’s husband dies, she starts hanging out with someone else’s daughter",
"answer": "Frozen II",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "ToxoTron",
"upvotes": "233",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/muwss8/after_womans_husband_dies_she_starts_hanging_out/"
},
{
"question": "Armed racists get trapped in a cabin together",
"answer": "The Hateful Eight",
"category": "Western",
"author": "itstuktyme",
"upvotes": "234",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/mfp0zd/armed_racists_get_trapped_in_a_cabin_together/"
},
{
"question": "Woman takes an (excessively?) long time to die",
"answer": "Kill Bill",
"category": "Action",
"author": "Entropyaardvark",
"upvotes": "230",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/kk2awx/woman_takes_an_excessively_long_time_to_die/"
},
{
"question": "A planet fails to sign something and gets destroyed...",
"answer": "The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "TheRealTilliamWell",
"upvotes": "234",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/db958c/a_planet_fails_to_sign_something_and_gets/"
},
{
"question": "Some guys invented a backpack to fend off a invasion.",
"answer": "Ghostbusters",
"category": "Comedy",
"author": "o0GamerGuy0o",
"upvotes": "230",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/crzrgs/some_guys_invented_a_backpack_to_fend_off_a/"
},
{
"question": "Elderly guy crosses international boundaries to escape being forced into a retirement home",
"answer": "Up",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "[deleted]",
"upvotes": "233",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/c90jgo/elderly_guy_crosses_international_boundaries_to/"
},
{
"question": "Woman tells her granddaughter the story of how she f**ked a guy she just met.",
"answer": "The Princess Bride",
"category": "Adventure",
"author": "DWPhoenix001",
"upvotes": "232",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/1epfcgi/woman_tells_her_granddaughter_the_story_of_how/"
},
{
"question": "A old man teaches a young boy how to be king by morphing him and breaking a girls heart",
"answer": "The Sword in the Stone",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "Ok_Ring_2287",
"upvotes": "231",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/ntajk8/a_old_man_teaches_a_young_boy_how_to_be_king_by/"
},
{
"question": "An old guy on a ship repeatedly asks for slippers",
"answer": "The Life Aquatic with Steve Zissou",
"category": "Comedy",
"author": "MrGamerMooseBTW",
"upvotes": "235",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/lj3t10/an_old_guy_on_a_ship_repeatedly_asks_for_slippers/"
},
{
"question": "Guy has split personality disorder, one of the personalities complains that the other is being more shy than normal",
"answer": "Fight Club",
"category": "Drama",
"author": "[deleted]",
"upvotes": "233",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/d0sn05/guy_has_split_personality_disorder_one_of_the/"
},
{
"question": "Dozens of diseased persons must rely on a PTSD-stricken vet in a life-or-death situation",
"answer": "Dawn of the Dead",
"category": "Horror",
"author": "twoscoopsofpig",
"upvotes": "232",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/nvnqwe/dozens_of_diseased_persons_must_rely_on_a/"
},
{
"question": "several people in multiple forms fuck up each other’s lives, or maybe make them better...or maybe neither.",
"answer": "Cloud Atlas",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "HoneyBDover",
"upvotes": "230",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/lch197/several_people_in_multiple_forms_fuck_up_each/"
},
{
"question": "A computer programmer with too many choices becomes more successful as he goes more insane.",
"answer": "The Matrix",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "Kate925",
"upvotes": "230",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/d8m6gn/a_computer_programmer_with_too_many_choices/"
},
{
"question": "This movie has it all - romance, betrayal, sword fights, poison,  and horseback rides",
"answer": "The Princess Bride",
"category": "Adventure",
"author": "see_bees",
"upvotes": "229",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/1ffdvhw/this_movie_has_it_all_romance_betrayal_sword/"
},
{
"question": "Multi layered film, in which fast food, is extremely popular.",
"answer": "Pulp Fiction",
"category": "Crime",
"author": "PH4NTON",
"upvotes": "226",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/ncuvqn/multi_layered_film_in_which_fast_food_is/"
},
{
"question": "A WWII veteran deals with PTSD by hooking up with his dead friend's wife.",
"answer": "Captain America: The First Avenger",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "[deleted]",
"upvotes": "229",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/mo0xby/a_wwii_veteran_deals_with_ptsd_by_hooking_up_with/"
},
{
"question": "Two scientists work on a purple serum, while a princess and her hunchbacked lover nuke historical monuments",
"answer": "Avengers: Age of Ultron",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "Sam2676789",
"upvotes": "232",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/de1oyb/two_scientists_work_on_a_purple_serum_while_a/"
},
{
"question": "Has-been TV star discovers obsessed stalker fan who wants $10M trying to break through his electric fence; they take a roadtrip together to put on one last show for a homeless man and his trashcan fire.",
"answer": "The Muppet Movie",
"category": "Comedy",
"author": "DramaGuy23",
"upvotes": "230",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/ddno94/hasbeen_tv_star_discovers_obsessed_stalker_fan/"
},
{
"question": "Brothers try to kill their sister. Their friend kills the sister's dog. Brothers claim victory by burning down their own home with their sister in it.",
"answer": "Toy Story",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "Doubletakkes",
"upvotes": "228",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/9vlh5w/brothers_try_to_kill_their_sister_their_friend/"
},
{
"question": "Visually the bloodiest movie ever.    Way bloodier than the last clue with this title.",
"answer": "Kill Bill: Vol. 1",
"category": "Action",
"author": "gipper1000",
"upvotes": "233",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/1jsvwuh/visually_the_bloodiest_movie_ever_way_bloodier/"
},
{
"question": "In the first 25 minutes of the movie, our two protagonists break into a coworker’s home to sexually harass them, almost murders the antagonist of the film, expose themselves at a public event, and get extremely drunk at a restaurant full of children",
"answer": "Minions: The Rise of Gru",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "StreetReporter",
"upvotes": "228",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/1g5159x/in_the_first_25_minutes_of_the_movie_our_two/"
},
{
"question": "The death of a construction foreman leads to the death of thousands.",
"answer": "Spider-Man",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "Dendallin",
"upvotes": "228",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/1eqsyjp/the_death_of_a_construction_foreman_leads_to_the/"
},
{
"question": "A guy pretends to be another guy, turns out to actually be that guy.",
"answer": "The Prestige",
"category": "Thriller",
"author": "MrShadowKing2020",
"upvotes": "227",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/mvrul3/a_guy_pretends_to_be_another_guy_turns_out_to/"
},
{
"question": "An insect allergy causes two characters to form an unlikely alliance. They team up and try to apprehend the real bad guys.",
"answer": "Ant-Man and the Wasp",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "sixmassageheads",
"upvotes": "227",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/kxf4la/an_insect_allergy_causes_two_characters_to_form/"
},
{
"question": "The world is saved using Imagination.",
"answer": "The Lego Movie",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "KaladinarLighteyes",
"upvotes": "233",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/kwbcpx/the_world_is_saved_using_imagination/"
},
{
"question": "There's a panda guy and he lives on an island with his friends and they get into a big fight and he wears a black suit with cat ears",
"answer": "Kung Fu Panda",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "elsiflor",
"upvotes": "226",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/c0dve5/theres_a_panda_guy_and_he_lives_on_an_island_with/"
},
{
"question": "A hero leaves his planet, meets a heart-of-gold rogue in a cantina, joins a rebellion against an evil empire with his beastly ally, and reunites with his lost twin sister. With ancient magic and an iconic energy-channeling sword, he destroys the empire's weapon of mass destruction.",
"answer": "Star Wars: Episode IV - A New Hope",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "EMike93309",
"upvotes": "227",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/1ht9snb/a_hero_leaves_his_planet_meets_a_heartofgold/"
},
{
"question": "A god becomes a musician to impress a woman.",
"answer": "Thor: Ragnarok",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "NickAndHisGuitar",
"upvotes": "226",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/lb3b7i/a_god_becomes_a_musician_to_impress_a_woman/"
},
{
"question": "Shakespearean Tragedy animated",
"answer": "The Lion King",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "nixxa13",
"upvotes": "230",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/l1votq/shakespearean_tragedy_animated/"
},
{
"question": "Military veteran turned POW comes home to find his family and fortune gone, and has to turn to crime with the son of a fellow prisoner.",
"answer": "The Shawshank Redemption",
"category": "Drama",
"author": "Jaleou",
"upvotes": "225",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/cmaynm/military_veteran_turned_pow_comes_home_to_find/"
},
{
"question": "An Arabian merchant tells you a long story so you’ll buy his antiques",
"answer": "Aladdin",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "Thegingerkid01",
"upvotes": "229",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/996lou/an_arabian_merchant_tells_you_a_long_story_so/"
},
{
"question": "A guy spends the entire movie trying to save his wife, then doesn't.",
"answer": "Interstellar",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "manchvegasnomore",
"upvotes": "225",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/1jcrxzf/a_guy_spends_the_entire_movie_trying_to_save_his/"
},
{
"question": "After his wife and most of his children are murdered by a serial killer a man must raise his only remaining child alone. When his child is kidnapped on his first day of school he must cross the ocean with a mentally handicapped woman to save him.",
"answer": "Finding Nemo",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "Coryfdw200",
"upvotes": "226",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/1i9y7z1/after_his_wife_and_most_of_his_children_are/"
},
{
"question": "Teenage girl becomes war refugee, sells herself to buy a farm, is widowed twice and abandoned by her 3rd husband",
"answer": "Gone with the Wind",
"category": "Drama",
"author": "scifiwoman",
"upvotes": "227",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/ocxaz8/teenage_girl_becomes_war_refugee_sells_herself_to/"
},
{
"question": "Vin Diesel plays a real lug head",
"answer": "The Iron Giant",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "terminal8",
"upvotes": "227",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/g1fz5n/vin_diesel_plays_a_real_lug_head/"
},
{
"question": "Dead man goes through mid life crisis",
"answer": "The Sixth Sense",
"category": "Thriller",
"author": "fludduck",
"upvotes": "226",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/cq2x78/dead_man_goes_through_mid_life_crisis/"
},
{
"question": "A mentally challenged man who loved his mama befriends an abused girl becomes an inspiration for many",
"answer": "Forrest Gump",
"category": "Drama",
"author": "igottathinkofaname",
"upvotes": "229",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/1eemkkp/a_mentally_challenged_man_who_loved_his_mama/"
},
{
"question": "Mad scientist kills almost everyone he meets, including his best friend.",
"answer": "Frankenstein",
"category": "Horror",
"author": "MintClicker",
"upvotes": "226",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/my7ubb/mad_scientist_kills_almost_everyone_he_meets/"
},
{
"question": "American invades foreign land, kills local leadership, then struggles to find an exit strategy.",
"answer": "Avatar",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "AuctionPicker",
"upvotes": "230",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/lw6v04/american_invades_foreign_land_kills_local/"
},
{
"question": "Handsome guy obsesses over a small toy as he struggles to get a grip on reality.",
"answer": "Inception",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "toru_okada_4ever",
"upvotes": "225",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/d33mt8/handsome_guy_obsesses_over_a_small_toy_as_he/"
},
{
"question": "A young woman meets a man incarcerated for his taste in cooking. Together; they work together to find a guy obsessed with sewing a cool suit for himself.",
"answer": "The Silence of the Lambs",
"category": "Thriller",
"author": "[deleted]",
"upvotes": "227",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/bhjlc9/a_young_woman_meets_a_man_incarcerated_for_his/"
},
{
"question": "Blue man cheats on his wife for his girlfriend, then cheat on his girlfriend for science.",
"answer": "Avatar",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "Burningmybread",
"upvotes": "227",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/bgri82/blue_man_cheats_on_his_wife_for_his_girlfriend/"
},
{
"question": "A guy goes to Norway to sleep inside an animal.",
"answer": "Star Wars: Episode V - The Empire Strikes Back",
"category": "Science Fiction",
"author": "young_fire",
"upvotes": "229",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/bdhkaw/a_guy_goes_to_norway_to_sleep_inside_an_animal/"
},
{
"question": "A single mother starts a new life with a career change. Her boss becomes infatuated with her and the leadership creates a toxic environment. She turns to an ex-boyfriend for help and protection, but he is arrested and the boss abducts her child in an attempt to force a relationship.",
"answer": "The Little Mermaid",
"category": "Animation",
"author": "DryWittgenstein",
"upvotes": "225",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/nttlr8/a_single_mother_starts_a_new_life_with_a_career/"
},
{
"question": "American veteran hitches a ride home after many years away from home",
"answer": "Captain America: The First Avenger",
"category": "Superhero",
"author": "EyeVee4",
"upvotes": "227",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/m1myo7/american_veteran_hitches_a_ride_home_after_many/"
},
{
"question": "[TV show] A world based mainly on a problem that can easily be solved by doctors, therapy or even a little encouragement...",
"answer": "The Good Doctor",
"category": "TV",
"author": "morrisonlikessamoyed",
"upvotes": "221",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/kuaws0/tv_show_a_world_based_mainly_on_a_problem_that/"
},
{
"question": "Wannabe chad keeps trying to make his crush fall for him but ends up nearly killing himself, getting kicked out of a club and even ruins her birthday",
"answer": "Scott Pilgrim vs. the World",
"category": "Comedy",
"author": "redditboy123451",
"upvotes": "224",
"permalink": "https://reddit.com/r/ExplainAFilmPlotBadly/comments/o5q8nq/wannabe_chad_keeps_trying_to_make_his_crush_fall/"
}
]